chitchats.com 2019-09-12

# Privacy Policy | Chit Chats

Effective December 1, 2016

By accessing this site, you agree that you have read and understand Chit Chats's (chitchats.com) privacy policy which describes how we use your personal information, and what options you have to update or request the deletion or correction of information submitted to us via chitchats.com. If you do not agree with the terms and conditions of this policy, please do not use the Site. 

##  **Your privacy is critically important to us. At Chit Chats we have a few fundamental principles:**

  * We won't ask you for personal information unless we really need it. 
  * We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights. 
  * We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services. 
  * In our service, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, kept private, and permanently deleted. 

It is Chit Chats' policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website. If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please send a message via our Contact Page. 

## **Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Chit Chats collects non-personal information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Chit Chats' purpose in collecting non-personally identifiable information is to better understand how Chit Chats' visitors use chitchats.com. From time to time, Chit Chats may release non-personal information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website. 

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Chit Chats uses cookies to help Chit Chats identify and track visitors, their usage of chitchats.com, and their website access preferences. chitchats.com visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using chitchats.com, with the drawback that certain features of Chit Chats may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

Chit Chats also collects potentially personally-identifiable information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Chit Chats does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personal information, as described below. 

## **Aggregated Statistics**

Chit Chats may collect information that does not contain personal information in order for the purpose of creating statistics about the behavior of visitors to Chit Chats. For instance, Chit Chats may monitor the most popular pages on the Chit Chats site. Chit Chats may display this information publicly or provide it to others. 

## **Protection of Certain Personally-Identifiable Information**

Chit Chats discloses potentially personal and personally-identifiable information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Chit Chats' behalf or to provide services available at chitchats.com, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country. By using Chit Chats, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. 

Chit Chats may disclose personal information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when Chit Chats believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Chit Chats, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of Chit Chats and have supplied your email address, Chit Chats may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Chit Chats and our services. You may change this setting in your account preferences. 

Chit Chats takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of personal information. 

## **Business Transfers**

If Chit Chats, or substantially all of its assets were acquired, or in the unlikely event that Chit Chats goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of Chit Chats may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy. 

## **Governing Law**

This policy, and all related matters are governed solely by the laws of British Columbia, Canada and applicable federal laws of Canada. Any dispute between you and Chit Chats or any other person arising from, connected with or relating to this Privacy Policy, or any related matters (collectively "Disputes") will be resolved solely in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

If there is any dispute arising out of or relating to this Privacy Policy, then the parties will first use reasonable and good faith efforts to resolve such dispute, first by direct negotiation and then, if that is not successful, by mediation with a neutral third party mediator acceptable to both parties. Each party will bear its own costs and expenses in connection with any mediation and all costs and expenses of the mediator will be shared equally by the parties. 

## **Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Chit Chats may change Chit Chats' Privacy Policy from time to time, and at Chit Chats' sole discretion. Chit Chats encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

## **Acknowledgment**

Chit Chats thanks Automattic for writing a straightforward [Privacy Policy](https://automattic.com/privacy/) and making it available under the [Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic License](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/).
